[Music]
remember Sunday morning. Quiet coffee
steam outside my door. Now it's sirens
every hour. Vengeance roaring endless
more. Traded black dot for a promise.
But the deal was one way signed.
Public boat without our warning. Left
our lives stuck in a line. Did you
count? Crashes climbing. Family stranded
on the curb. Shuffle papers did the
study. Just pretend it's not absurd.
All the cars losing patience. Jammed in
front of my home. Frog cake park
while we stuck in the zone. Suns and
Richmond left behind in endless horns
and fields. No one asked what happens
here. Democracy left the room.
No way out, no way through.
Overflow on avenues.
Lines of metal neverending. Kids dodging
double yellow speed.
Nights haunted by engines blending with
baults. No one ever read or eats.
Where's our air that's not from tail
fight stacking up from blocks? Shut it
through without a study while they bear
patty facts in talks. Said it's free
to run. Ignore the folks who live in our
voices never heard losing patience.
Jammed in front of my home. Rocket
watching for tourists while we're stuck
in the zone. Sunset Richmond left behind
inless horns and fields. No one asked
what happens here. Democracy left.
No way. I'm no way through.
Open Avenue.
[Music]
All the cars losing patience jammed in
front of my home. Sunset Richmond left
behind in endless horns and fields. No
one ask what happens here. Democracy
left the room.
[Music]